Future Histories UP274
Tufts Archival Research Center
Future Histories
2017 -- 2022
Tufts Archival Research Center
UP274
0.25 Linear Feet
7 Digital Object(s)
157 Megabytes
This collection contains issues of Future Histories, a literary magazine published by Tufts students.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains print and digital issues of Future Histories, a literary magazine published by Tufts students.
Biographical / Historical
Future Histories is a student-run literary magazine at Tufts University. It began publication in Fall 2017 and is published semi-annually. Future Histories publishes Tufts students' creative writing, studio art, and photography, with an emphasis on featuring diverse work from marginalized voices.
Future Histories was founded by Tufts juniors Sarah Walsh and Hunter Silvestri, partially in response to the lack of literary publication on campus after the Cannon Literary Journal ceased publication in Fall 2016. The founders made efforts to reach out to cultural clubs on campus and encourage students from diverse backgrounds to submit their work, including in languages other than English. The publication also supports larger and more experimental student work in separate side issues.
- Future Histories, 2017 -- 2022; UP274.000001
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains print and digital issues of Future Histories, a literary magazine published by Tufts students.
  - Future Histories, Fall 2017; UP274.000006; 8.29 Megabytes
    Issue
    0
  - Future Histories, Spring 2018; UP274.000002; 22.23 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    1
  - Future Histories, Fall 2018; UP274.000003; 30.13 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    e 2
  - Future Histories, Spring 2019; UP274.000004; 25.22 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 3)
    3
  - Future Histories, Fall 2019; UP274.000005; 58.14 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    4
  - Future Histories, Fall 2020; UP274.000007; 5.42 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 5)
    5
  - Future Histories, Spring 2021; UP274.000008; 7.94 Megabytes
    6
  - Future Histories, Fall 2021; UP274.000009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Lauren Fischer, 2022, accession UP-2023-045
    7
  - Future Histories, Spring 2022; UP274.000010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    8
  - Future Histories, Fall 2022; UP274.000011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    9